He's Her Work In Progress
The Makeover is a comedy film directed by John Gray.
This is an update of George Bernard Shaw's "Pygmalion" that
changes the genders of the main characters.
Hannah Higgins attempts to turn blue-collar Boston beer vendor Elliot Doolittle into a
viable candidate and inadvertently learns something of Elliot's side of life.
Hannah, played by Julia Stiles.
Elliot, played by David Walton.
Colleen, played by Camryn Manheim.
Allie Doolittle, played by Frances Fisher.
Frank, played by Tony Viveiros.
Wilma, played by Nada Despotovich.
The following is a list of episodes of the American
television anthology series, Hallmark Hall of Fame.
(v) indicates the production is available on videocassette.
(DVD) indicates the movie is available on DVD
The tone is lighthearted.